

Shih-Ting, Yu

UIUX Designer

Birth Phone Email

1994.01.29 0935830129 janetyu0129@gmail.com

About

Hi, I'm a UIUX designer with 5+ years of experience in the user interface design industry. UI designer with creative and detail-oriented skills. Currently works as a senior UI designer in ASUS Cloud Corporation, Built landing page design experience at ASUS Cloud, reaching a 1 million in revenue within one month, and an 80% decrease in customer complaints rate. From these experiences, I learned that in addition to basic skills, designers should be able to observe GA data continuously to achieve a better user experience, truly grasp the needs of users, and express the meaning and value of design. I believe that repeated discussions and verifications will surely bring a more intuitive and friendly design experiences.

Education

Information Management at Fu Jen University

2012 - 2016

English Abilities

TOEIC

840

GEPT

High-intermediate

Skills











Work Experiences

ASUS Cloud Corporation

UI Designer / 2019.07 - Now

- Design a landing page successfully reached 1 million revenue within one month of launch.
- Reduced customer complaints rate by 80% after product function optimization.

Lion Information Technology Corporation

UX Designer / 2018.03 - 2019.07

 Homepage successfully added 500,000 new users within three months after redesign.

Egroup Corporation

Graphic & UIUX Designer / 2015.12 - 2017.10







Autobiography

My name is Janet. I hold a bachelor's degree with a major in Information Management which was awarded to me by Fu-Jen University in 2016. I had been working as a UI Designer for over 5 years, currently work in ASUS Cloud Company, which is one of the most promising companies in the technology industry in Taiwan. I mainly executed UIUX design in my position, successfully reached 1 million revenue within one month of landing page design launch, and reduced customer complaints by 80% after product function optimization.

"There is no best to design, only better." After thoroughly reviewing the past experience, I decided to only learn the lesson and not look back. For me, the past is a valuable experience that can be used as a guide. Now, through the relevant training and refinement, I have grown more confident to be a better UIUX designer, and the elements such as color, text, buttons, icons, etc. can be flexibly controlled, visual design, production, modification, writing, and so on can be performed efficiently. I have great enthusiasm for UIUX design, I hope to get a chance to prove myself.

My short-term goal is to find a position where I can use the design knowledge and strengths I have. Ultimately, I look forward to becoming a full-end designer, and I would love to assume more management responsibilities and get more involved in business strategy.

With my experiences and profession in UIUX design, I believe I am ready for this position, and I will definitely develop myself to keep pace with the changes of the era in this field.







